(Amy:)Play with your phone.
(Alfred:)Well, on that note,
(Alfred:)there are many cultures
that have an apocalyptic flood
(Alfred:)as part of their mythology.
(Mary:)I don't have a mythology.
(Mary:)I have the unerring Word of God.
(Mary:)But that's very interesting.
(Leonard:)Oh.
I-I didn't mean to
disparage your faith.
(Alfred:)Actually, I admire it.
(Mary:)Really?
Yes.
(Alfred:)Yes, I'm an agnostic myself,
(Alfred:)but I have prayed,
many times, to God,
(Alfred:)to turn my wife
into a pillar of salt.
(Mary:)Well, He came close.
(Mary:)Turned her into
a giant block of ice.
(both laughing)
(Raj:)Howard, there must be someone
at the university
(Raj:)you can go to for help.
(Howard:)Are you kidding?
(Howard:)They're probably the ones
who leaked it
(Howard:)to the military
in the first place.
(Raj:)What about the guy
on the Channel Four News?
(Penny:)You know,
"Four on Your Side"?
Maybe he can be on your side.
(Howard:)I'm being harassed
by the government,